downloadastro.com 2018-03-21

# Downloadastro privacy policy

Written in accordance with the provisions of Law 677/2001, regarding individual protection about collecting and free circulation of personal data. 

Downloadastro.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy over the internet. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Downloadastro. 

During the administration process of the website, Downloadastro needs to take over some personal information, in order to personalize the website usage and make it easier for each one of the users. Also, collecting information (such as name, e-mail etc) is useful for Downloadastro.com in order to adapt our ads to your preferences. Downloadastro.com respects and grants confidentiality for personal data collected over from its users at several different points on the website. We are the sole owners of the information gathered within the Downloadastro.com website. We shall not sell or rent this information to others in any way. We shall not share this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

The clauses of this policy are valuable for all kinds of information gathered from Downloadastro users. Additional clauses, if any, will be added if necessary for special services that we may offer in the future. This privacy policy informs you about the type of personal data that we may collect from you, the way we can use it, the way we understand to protect it, who has access to it and how the possible mistakes can be corrected. 

**Information that we collect**  
Downloadastro may collect information from its users in three different ways: directly from the user, from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies. 

Information provided directly by the user: when you subscribe to a service provided by Downloadastro, we may ask you about your name, e-mail address or other personal data. For example, when you register to our website, you may need to enter your username, e-mail address and password. 

Information from traffic references: when you visit a website, you unveil certain information about you, such as your IP address, time of visit, place from which you accessed our website. Downloadastro, like other operators, stores this information. 

Information collected from cookies: in order to offer you a personalized service, Downloadastro may use cookies to ease storing and tracking your preferences. For instance, we may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, or to deliver content specific to your interests; the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

Cookies are "txt" files offered to your browser by a web server and then stored on the hard-disk of your computer. Most of browsers are set to accept cookies. But if you prefer, you can reset your browser so as to let you know whenever you receive a cookie or even to refuse cookies. However, you should know that some parts of Downloadastro website can only be normally seen if your browser allows cookies. 

Downloadastro allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Downloadastro site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Downloadastro site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Downloadastro does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Downloadastro to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Downloadastro Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

You need to acknowledge that, whenever you disclose information in public areas on the website, such as message boards (comments) or forums, that information becomes public and can easily be tracked and used by unauthorized persons. Although Downloadastro.com does its best in order to protect your personal data, we cannot entirely grant you its safety. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. You should also know that you are the only one responsible for keeping the secret of your passwords, usernames etc. 

**How and when we use the information**  
Downloadastro uses the information collected from you for several purposes, depending on the type of data collected:  
\- information provided directly by the user: this information is used only in order to personalize the services that we offer you and to check your identity;  
\- information from traffic references: this type of info helps us identify the parts of our site of most interest for you. Downloadastro also collects the IP addresses of its users, in order to safely manage our computer system;  
\- information collected from cookies: Downloadastro uses cookies to help you with our services and with getting statistic information for the services improvement. Cookies allow us to save your passwords and your preferences so that you do not have to introduce them again at your next visit. 

**How we protect information collected from you**  
We show great interest in confidentiality. Downloadastro.com does not offer your personal data to third parties without your prior express consent. Any statistics that we may offer to our partners or to advertisement networks does not include any personal identifying information about any individual user.

Your access to certain services on the website may be protected by a password. In such case we advise you not to unveil this password to anyone. Downloadastro will never ask for the password of your accounts through any kind of messages or unsolicited phone calls. We strongly advise you not to unveil your passwords to those who may ask you to. As a plus, if possible, you should remember to click "log off" / "sign out", at the end of any working session in your account. We also advise you to close your browser window when you quit using the sites or the services provided by Downloadastro.com. 

These pieces of advice are meant to restrain the access of unauthorized persons to your personal information or mail, especially when you work in a computer network in a public place (net cafe for example).

Unfortunately, no data transmission by means of internet can be 100% sure. As a consequence, despite our efforts to protect your personal data, Downloadastro.com cannot guarantee the safety of your information. All this kind of transmission whatsoever is made on your own risk. 

Still, we can grant you that we carry out all our efforts to ensure safety for our systems, according to the security standards imposed by Romanian legislation. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff checks server access daily to ensure the above holds true. 

**Unsolicited communication**  
Downloadastro will not use your e-mail address in order to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail. It is your choice whether you decide to receive or not newsletters from us. You can always choose to unsubscribe from our newsletter services. 

**Who has access to the information collected from you**  
As a rule, Downloadastro.com will never unveil any sort of personally identifiable information about any of its users, without their prior express consent. On the other hand, Downloadastro.com may unveil this kind of data when expressly permitted by law or when this measure is necessary in order to protect Downloadastro rights and interests.

As a conclusion, when you access Downloadastro website and are asked to offer information about you, only Downloadastro.com will have access to them. However, you acknowledge that our site contains links to some partner sites. Downloadastro is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. We do not share this information with third parties.

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use [DART cookies](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**How we can correct errors contained by data collected from you**  
If you create an account to one of our services, we shall send you a confirmation e-mail in which we give you the details of the newly created account. The confirmation message will be sent at the e-mail address that you provided. We strongly advise you to keep this confirmation mail secret, because it contains information that can be useful when you encounter problems in accessing our services. 

**Children's Guidelines**  
This site gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Downloadastro. For any suggestions and comments regarding Downloadastro or our Privacy Policy, please contact us. 

This Privacy Policy has been updated today, 7th of November, 2012.
